bitlord.com 2019-07-10

# BitLord - Privacy Policy

Date of last revision May 14, 2018

BitLord by House of Life Property ltd. (BitLord) is committed to respecting the privacy rights and concerns of all users of our websites ("Sites"), applications and services (collectively, the "Services"). As such, we have established and implemented this privacy policy to inform visitors to the Sites and users of the Services how we use and protect the information we collect. If you have any questions regarding this information or our privacy practices, please see the section entitled "Questions? Contact Us" at the end of this privacy policy.

What information does BitLord collect and how does BitLord use it?

HOW THE BitLord CLIENT WORKS

The BitLord Client is a software application on your machine that manages downloads. It downloads files quickly by trading pieces with other users who are also downloading (or have downloaded) the same content. Your use of the BitLord Client to download files will, in turn, enable other BitLord users (or users of other clients that communicate using the BitLord protocol, including clients that are unaffiliated with BitLord, Inc.) to download pieces of those files from you. Although your IP address is associated with your piece of the file, other users will not have access to any other personal information about you.

We do not track which files you transfer with the BitLord Client. Merely using the BitLord Client does not cause a record of which files you transfer to be kept by BitLord or BitLord on behalf of any third party.

GATHERING AND USE OF ANONYMOUS INFORMATION

Each time a visitor comes to one of our Sites (including bitlord.com), we collect some limited information that your browser routinely makes available whenever you visit a website. We collect this data to improve the overall quality of the online experience, including product monitoring, product improvement, and targeted advertising. This information includes your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

In addition to collecting these types of information, BitLord collects aggregate queries for internal reporting and targeted advertising. We also count, track, and aggregate the visitor's activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our websites (e.g. tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the websites, etc.). To these ends, we may merge information about you into group data, which may then be shared on an aggregated basis with our advertisers; but BitLord will not disclose your individual identity or personal data without your permission.

In the event that you provide us with answers to voluntary survey questions, we may present this information to our advertisers and partners, in the form of grouped statistics compiled from our users’ answers to such questions.

We also aggregate some data from the BitLord Client regarding total traffic flows and content delivery performance as well as other data collected in the use of our products or services in order to understand usability and monitor network conditions and compare the performance of BitLord and HTTP protocols on the public internet. End users may opt out of providing this information using a Preferences setting.

GATHERING AND USE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

You may visit the Sites and use the BitLord Client and many of the Services without any registration at all. However, from time to time, we may enable certain additional functionality or services whereby you will have to create a user account, and we may collect and process the following information about you:

information such as your name, address, phone number and e-mail address, and other demogaphic information (such as date of birth, gender, age, and interests) that you provide by completing forms on the Sites, including if you register as a user of the Services, subscribe to our mailing lists, upload or submit any material through the services, or request any information.

your log-in and password details in connection with the account sign-in process;

details of any requests or transactions made by you throughthe Service;

communications you send to us, for example to report a problem or to submit queries, concerns, or comments regarding the Service or its content;

information that you post to the Site in the form of comments or contributions to discussions; and

IP addresses.  
We will use the personal information you provide to:

identify you when you sign-in to your account;

enable us to provide you with the Services;

send you information we think you may find useful or which you have requested from us;

present projects to you when you use the Service which we believe will be of interest based on your geographic location and previous use of the Service;

administer your account with us;

enable us to contact you regarding any question you make through the Service;

analyze the use of the Service and the people visiting to improve our content and Services; and  
use for other purposes that we may disclose to you when we request your information.

We may also use e-mail addresses and other personally identifiable information from time to time in order to gather and provide to our members and visitors improved content and features.

Notwithstanding any other term of this Privacy Policy, we may release any personal information we obtain or collect when we believe its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our Site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.

How does BitLord protect customer information?  
We implement a variety of security measures to ensure the security of your personal information on our systems. User personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to such systems.

Does BitLord use "cookies"?  
Cookies are small bits of electronic information that a web site can transfer to a visitor's hard drive to help tailor and keep records of his or her visit to the site. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many web sites use them. Cookies allow web site operators to better customize visits to the site to the visitor's individual preferences. For example, by setting a cookie you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time. We currently save password information in cookies. In addition, advertisements displayed on the BitLord websites or in the BitLord Client may contain cookies. The companies who serve our advertisements transfer cookies independent of us, and, as such, we do not control the use of such cookies and in many instances have no access to the information collected by them.

Although most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, you can usually change your browser to prevent that or to notify you when you are sent a cookie. Even without accepting a cookie, you can still access many, if not all, of the features of the BitLord websites or the BitLord Client. However, some parts of the BitLord websites or the BitLord Client may not function properly if you refuse cookies.

Does BitLord disclose the information it collects from its visitors to outside parties?  
BitLord does not currently sell, trade, or otherwise transfer outside the company personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily provide in any registration or use of the BitLord websites or the BitLord Client. This information is used to better understand visitors’ use of the features of the BitLord websites or the BitLord Client, to support related transactions made on or through the BitLord websites or the BitLord Client, and to better know our visitors and possibly tailor any specific features, promotions, or other notifications to them. However, this data in an aggregate form without any personally identifiable information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Finally, we may disclose your personally identifiable information upon a transfer or sale to another entity of all or substantially all of our assets or equity securities or upon any other corporate reorganization.

BitLord’s special note to parents.  
In compliance with the 1998 Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), the Sites are general audience websites, and do not knowingly collect, nor will it ever knowingly retain, personally identifiable information from any visitor BitLord actually knows to be under thirteen years of age without the consent of that child's parent or legal guardian.

Third party links and co-brand relationships.  
In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, we may choose various third party web sites or services to link to, and/or frame within, the Sites or Services. We may also include offers from third parties as part of the installation process for our software. We also participate in co-branding and other relationships to offer e-commerce and other services and features to our users. However, even if the third party is affiliated with us, we have no control over these third party sites or services, each of which has separate privacy and data collection practices independent of us. Data collected by our co-brand partners or third party web sites (even if offered on or through our Site or Services) may not be received by us. As such, we have no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any such web sites or services. These linked sites or services are only for your convenience and you therefore access them at your own risk. We may use [third-party advertising companies](http://d391xajlu8p371.cloudfront.net/pp.html) to serve ads when you visit our website.

Notification of changes.  
By visiting the website or using the applications and/or services, you consent to the collection and use of information by us as set forth in this privacy policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes within this page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

Questions? Contact us.  
If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please do not hesitate to write to us through our online support form.

Please also read any applicable End User License Agreements that apply to individual BitLord applications and services.
